Easterners, the Fatherland or the grave!
Liberty or with glory we die!
It is the vow that the soul pronounces,
and which, heroically we will fulfill!
and which, heroically we will fulfill.
Which we will fulfill!
It is the vow that the soul pronounces,
and which, heroically we will fulfill.
Which we will fulfill,
we will fulfill.
We will fulfill!
Liberty, Liberty, Easterners!
This cry saved the fatherland.
Which her brave warriors, in fierce battles with sublime enthusiasm fill'd.
This Holy gift of Glory we have deserved.
Tyrants: Tremble! Tyrants: Tremble! Tyrants: Tremble! Ah!
Liberty in combat we will Cry Out! And even dying, Freedom we shall also Shout!
And even dying, Freedom we shall also Shout!
Freedom we shall also Shout!
Easterners, our nation or the grave!
Liberty or with glory we die!
Easterners, our nation or the grave, Liberty or with glory we die!
It’s the vow that the soul pronounces,
and which, heroically we will fulfill.
It’s the vow that the soul pronounces, and which, heroically we will fulfill.
Which we will fulfill!
It’s the vow that the soul pronounces, and which, heroically we will fulfill. Which we will fulfill!
We will fulfill!